Abhyuday Pratap Singh

I am a passionate technologist who loves to create web experiences that are engaging and visually appealing and I am currently in my 2nd year and pursuing a B.. Tech in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning from Maharaja Agrasen Institute of Technology.

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

+91 6391909757

apsworks1212@gmail.com

Q Delhi, India

https://abhyuday.netlify.app/

SKILLS

- Front End Development (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
- React
- C/C++
- Java
- DSA
- React
- Web Extensions
- Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY - 8 CGPA

Maharaja Agrasen Institute Of Technology 2022 - Present

12'TH - 78.8%

Madhav Public Scool 2021

10'TH - 94.8%

Alma Mater The School 2019

LANGUAGE

English Hindi

EXPERIENCE

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR

<u>Unstop</u>

2023 - Present

- I gather valuable feedback from peers and offer insights to the company, contributing to continuous improvements in products or services.
- I actively engage in promoting the company's brand to enhance its visibility and recognition on campus.
- I facilitate the generation of ideas for campaigns and product development.

OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTOR

Social Summer Of Code

June, 2023 - July, 2023 (2 Months)

- Enhanced #SSOC'23 project with #1270+ additions.
- Converted basic calculator into a scientific one with advanced functions.
- User-friendly interface, accessible on mobile and desktop.

PROJECTS

SICI - FI CALC

- Inverse and standard trigonometric, exponential, logarithmic functions, and more.
- Parentheses support, factorial, constants, nth root, and inverse functions added.
- A comprehensive set of advanced features for an enriched user experience.

AWARDS

 Ranked #9 Out of 5000+ contributor who participated in SSOC'23 by GitHub during 1 June, 2023 - 31 July, 2023 for Contributing in Front-End-Projects repository for most Number Of Additions.